[dotenv@17.2.3] injecting env (4) from .env -- tip: Ô£à audit secrets and track compliance: https://dotenvx.com/ops
--- ADDING COLUMNS TO quotations TABLE ---

[!] IMPORTANT: Columns "budget" and "success_probability" are MISSING in Supabase.
Since I cannot run SQL ALTER TABLE via JS client, please run this in your Supabase SQL Editor:

ALTER TABLE quotations ADD COLUMN budget DOUBLE PRECISION DEFAULT 0;
ALTER TABLE quotations ADD COLUMN success_probability DOUBLE PRECISION DEFAULT 0;
